# SHAHAR ARIEL

B.Sc. in Software Engineering

ShaharAriel95@gmail.com | 050-880-2266 | LinkedIn | GitHub

# **PROFILE**

Motivated Full Stack Developer with an ability in NodeJS, Angular, Vue, and MongoDB. Proven record of successfully executing projects in Internet Web Services and Web and Cloud development. Recent professional experience includes a role at Uniper-Care, where I sharpened my skills in building and maintaining web applications.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

2023 - 2024	Uniper-care – Empowering older adults through connected and active living. Full Stack Developer
	Responsible for developing and integrating new features to enhance and maintain
	the platform capabilities, utilizing NodeJS, Angular, Vue, and MongoDB.
2021 –2022	Percepto Robotics - Autonomous inspection & monitoring for industrial sites.
	Technical support
	Solving software and hardware problems in the company products for clients worldwide.
	Work with Linux environment, log analysis and extraction in Bash terminal.
2019-2020	Marketing and export management of Kedma Ltd. Moshav Idan.
2016-2017	Manually tested Elbit System software while serving in the IDF

### PROJECT AND SKILLS

- Final Project SignMyName a Deep learning and Computer vision education app to teach kids the Israeli Sign Language Alpha Bet Using Machine learning gesture recognition: TensorFlow – CNN, OpenCV2, TKINTER, MediaPipe
- Internet Web Services Created and oversaw the IAM of an AB Test website, while also in charge of the DB and the Data transfers between teams. Worked in Node.js, Express, MongoDB, and React
- Programming languages: Python OOP, JavaScript, C, Java, C++, Linux Bash, HTML, CSS
- Courses Image Processing and Computer vision, Practical ML, Cloud Computing

#### **EDUCATION**

B.Sc. degree in software engineering at Shenkar College – Engineering faculty.
Second Position: faculty instructor – responsible for the professional training
in command-and-control system in the Armored corps.
Tank Commander – Service in the Combat units in the Armored corps

## ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- Languages: Hebrew (native speaker), English (fluent)
- **Volunteer:** 2020 2021: Mitchashvim: Solving software and hardware problems in the company products for clients worldwide, was in charge of getting and distributing computers.